SAORIOKAWA

Certified UX Designer

CONTACT

- +31642947663
- ✓ saoriokawa@gmail.com
- The Hague
- saoriokawa.github.io/portfolio
- in www.linkedin.com/in/saoriokawa
- Bē www.behance.net/saoriokawa

TOOLS

Sketch FlowMapp
InVision Usability Hub
Adobe XD Optimal Workshop
Balsamiq MS Office

UX SKILLS

Competitive Analysis
User Interviews
User Personas
Journey Maps
Information Architecture
Wireframing and Prototyping
Usability Testing
HTML/CSS

LANGUAGES

JAPANESE: Native ENGLISH: Fluent DUTCH: Basic ITALIAN: Basic



PROFILE

I am a teacher-turned-UX designer with curiosity in understanding people as well as organisational skills to make complicated information easy to comprehend.

I can offer a high sensitivity for details and rigidity in getting a job done, which I have acquired through my four years of experience as a translation checker.



WORK EXPERIENCE

AUG 2019-Current

UX Design Intern

LinkPT, US (Remote)

- Working remotely as a part of a startup company in New York.
- Collaborating with the team of product manager, developers, designers and therapists to create intuitive, user-friendly software.
- · Establishing user flows and wireframing.

AUG 2016-Current

Freelancer

The Netherlands

- Moving to a foreign country and working as as self-employed.
- Providing translation check service between Japanese and English.
- Managing translation projects.
- Giving Japanese/English lessons.

APR 2015-AUG 2016

Quality Control Manager

ASCA Corporation, Japan

- Managing medical translation projects contacting clients and contractors.
- Coordinating courses in medical patent translation.
- Spreading the use of a translation software among company and its contractors.

JAN 2014-MAR 2015

English Instructor

ECC, Japan

- Teaching English to students including kids and adults.
- $\bullet \ \ \text{Managing 16 classes with about 100 students in total cooperating with school staff.}$

APR 2013-NOV 2013

Transactional Specialist

Arvato Digital Services, Singapore

• Corresponding to email enquiries to process registration and to make contracts.



EDUCATION

2018-19

UX Design Course

CareerFoundry

- Developed several real-world projects during the course, using software such as Adobe XD, Sketch and Balsamiq.
- Building a portfolio website using HTML/CSS, GitHub and JavaScript with the guide from an industry-leading mentor.

2011-13

2007-11

MSc Management with Merit

University of Leicester, UK

BA Intercultural Studies with GPA 3.6

Kobe University, Japan